First psychotherapy talk therapy. This includes
a cognitive behavioral therapy.
CBT helps individuals identify and challenge
irrational thoughts and behaviors that contribute to anxiety.
It provides practical strategies to manage anxiety
effectively. B exposure Therapy
this technique gradually exposes individuals
to the situations or objects they fear, helping them build
tolerance and reduce anxiety responses.
C mindfulnessbased therapies mindfulnessbased
approaches such as mindfulnessbased stress reduction,
MBSR and mindfulness based cognitive therapy
teach individuals to stay present and reduce excessive
worry.